I want to see you sitting around the table with orphans,
eating with them and the elderly, giving them a kiss.
The one we can give to God through the needy,
the one you can give to God through the less privileged,
the one you can give to God through
widows,
the one you can give to God through widowers,
the one you can give to God through physically challenged
is the one you will give with all your heart,
with a smile, without murmuring or complaining.
When you give it, you are giving it to God
and God will bless you in abundance.
Have you been doing that?
No.
You give with complaining.
You give with murmuring.
You are always complaining when you want to give;
even when you want to give tithe and now give it out.
You don't even need to talk.
Once it is change you received from the conductor,
once it is change you received from the petrol station,
once it is change, it is a way of saying, "Change"
and you receive change in return.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can't see God but you give the less privileged.
Through the less privileged to God.
It's God we are giving but through them.
He has no hands but our hands to do His work.
He has no legs but our legs to go where He wants to go.
He has no mouth to explain Himself How He was crucified
but our mouth to do that.
If you give in the name of Jesus, you will never regret.
But in the name of selfish, classic and material reasons,
for reasons known to you, you give this,
you will regret it because man can never be trusted.
The giving you have done in the past, you think it's lost;
it is not lost.
If it is in the name of God,
you will receive the reward at a time you need it most.
That is what has happened to many of you.
Sometimes you see help just come at the very time you need it.
But you have forgotten you have done it to someone in the past.
One can never get to any place or any position without genuine giving.
If you don't give your love genuinely,
you can never and you will never receive genuine love from people.
As you lay your bed, you sleep on it.
The more you give, the greater your money, if you give genuinely,
not giving whilst murmuring or complaining.
When you are giving it, you begin to complain,
"What will I eat? How will I go about it? What will happen to me next?"
That is, you have nullified the processing.
Begin to give. That is my life for you.
When you are giving, you have to believe God and trust Him
that He's the one you are giving to.
See your contribution as an assignment from God.
Look at what I'm doing now. I'm talking to you.
It is an assignment from God.
I'm looking at you. It is an assignment from God.
Give me your hand. It is an assignment from God.
I'm not seeing it as helping you
but as an assignment given to me from God.
And I'm not expecting a reward from you. God is my Rewarder.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When you see it as an assignment from God,
you will not expect a reward from the person you are helping.
So, please give so that you will be very great.
Your greatness depends on your giving.
Tell your neighbour, My greatness depends on my giving.
When you give fast, you'll be great fast.
When you give slowly, you'll be great slowly.
When you give small, you'll be great small, small, small!
You're an angel of God!
An angel of God that gives love of God.
I'm an angel of God that gives love of God,
kindness of God, goodness of God, humility, faithfulness!
I'm an angel of God!
Be bold to say, I'm an angel of God!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Many of us here, in one way or the other,
you have accused some of our elderly to be witches or wizards.
Please, it is time to reconcile!
Attacks are meant for our spiritual benefit.
So, please, it is time to reconcile.
You have accused any of our mummy, daddy, elderly to be a witch or wizard
or some of the gods - the small small gods
which you created by yourself
and you now put it in the cupboard and worship it -
is now the one telling you, "This person is a witch, this one is a wizard".
Please, go back and say, sorry.
Give a kiss and put everything behind you.
Put it behind you.
Just put everything behind you.
And it is an opportunity now for those you have not been greeting
and they have not been greeting you,
you say, "Over my dead body, I will never greet them!" -
it is an opportunity for reconciliation!
Just go there, give them a call, "Oh, how are you? I miss you! Long time!"
"Who is on the line?"
"I miss you!" - keep saying, "I miss you!"
Even if satan hears, "I miss you!", he'll want to listen to you.
"I miss you!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Give a call to those of whom you believe, "No, I will never call them!
I will never have anything to do with them!"
Give them a call!
Please.
If you can use this occasion to settle with people you see as your enemies,
the sky will be your limit.
If enemies can stop people, I would have been stopped.
They are there to test your faith.
Testing or attacks or challenges you are talking about is the beauty in our journey.
Anytime there is trouble that disturbs you, it is an opportunity to be promoted.
Instead, you think otherwise.
I know God has prepared you for this journey.
You can start doing the job on the phone.
People you have not been speaking to for many years,
for one reason or the other - please, make a phone call.
Rededicate yourself, please.
I declare here I have not done enough.
It is true that I give to the needy, less privileged, orphans
but I now realise that I have not done enough.
Rise up. Let me pray with you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Your love for one another is not enough.
Your care for one another is not enough.
And what is not done well is not done at all.
Open your lips and begin to cry to God.
Give me the grace, Lord, to love one another.
I want to be a cheerful giver.
Give me the grace, Lord.
A heart that loves, a heart that cares.
I need You more and more
I need You more and more Jesus every day
Like a flower needs the rain
Like a bird needs the wind
I need You more and more Jesus every day
I need You more and more
Like a flower needs the rain
Like a bird needs the wind
I need You more and more Jesus every day
Like a flower needs the rain
Like a bird needs the wind
I need You more and more Jesus every day
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Lord Jesus, give us a heart that loves, a heart that cares, in Jesus Christ's name.
You may be seated.
God bless you, thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service